{
  "medium": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Who did Manchester United beat in the Quarter-Final on their way to winning the Champions League in 1999?",
      "option_a": "Borussia Dortmund",
      "option_b": "Valencia",
      "option_c": "Inter Milan",
      "option_d": "Dynamo Kiev",
      "correct": "Inter Milan"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "When did Manchester United first win the FA Cup?",
      "option_a": "1909",
      "option_b": "1928",
      "option_c": "1912",
      "option_d": "1935",
      "correct": "1909"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "What club did Manchester United sign Ruud Van Nistelrooy from?",
      "option_a": "Ajax",
      "option_b": "Feyenoord",
      "option_c": "PSV Eindhoven",
      "option_d": "FC Twente",
      "correct": "PSV Eindhoven"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Which team did Manchester United beat to win the 1991 Cup Winners Cup?",
      "option_a": "AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Paris St Germain",
      "option_c": "Porto",
      "option_d": "Barcelona",
      "correct": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "United had gone 40 years without defeat in European competition at home but their run was ended in the 1996-97 tournament. Which team ended that run?",
      "option_a": "Dynamo Kiev",
      "option_b": "Sporting Lisbon",
      "option_c": "Deportivo La Coruna",
      "option_d": "Fenerbache",
      "correct": "Fenerbache"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Where did United sign Steve Bruce from?",
      "option_a": "Norwich City",
      "option_b": "Aston Villa",
      "option_c": "Birmingham City",
      "option_d": "Hull City",
      "correct": "Norwich City"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Who was the first Manchester United captain from outside the United Kingdom or the Republic of Ireland?",
      "option_a": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_b": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_c": "Nemanja Vidic",
      "option_d": "Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Eric Cantona"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "Who became Manchester United's Record signing in 2002?",
      "option_a": "Juan Sebastian Veron",
      "option_b": "Rio Ferdinand",
      "option_c": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_d": "Wayne Rooney",
      "correct": "Rio Ferdinand"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "From which of these clubs was Ole Gunnar Solskjaer signed?",
      "option_a": "FK Brann",
      "option_b": "Valaerenga",
      "option_c": "Lillestrom",
      "option_d": "Molde",
      "correct": "Molde"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Which team did Brian McClair join Manchester United from?",
      "option_a": "Cork City",
      "option_b": "Celtic",
      "option_c": "Aberdeen",
      "option_d": "Cardiff City",
      "correct": "Celtic"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "Against which team did Dwight Yorke open up his Manchester United account?",
      "option_a": "Charlton Athletic",
      "option_b": "West Ham",
      "option_c": "Derby County",
      "option_d": "Everton",
      "correct": "Charlton Athletic"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "From what club did Manchester United sign Andrei Kanchelskis?",
      "option_a": "Fiorentina",
      "option_b": "Saturn Moscow Oblast",
      "option_c": "Dyanmo Kiev",
      "option_d": "Shakhtar Donetsk",
      "correct": "Shakhtar Donetsk"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "After drawing the first leg 1-1, United beat Juventus in a thrilling second leg 3-2 to reach the 1999 Champions League final. Who scored the winner?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Andy Cole",
      "option_d": "Roy Keane",
      "correct": "Andy Cole"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "Manchester United have won the UEFA Super Cup just once. In what year did they win it and who did they beat?",
      "option_a": "Lazio in 1999",
      "option_b": "Zenit St Petersburg in 2008",
      "option_c": "Real Madrid in 2017",
      "option_d": "Red Star Belgrade in 1991",
      "correct": "Red Star Belgrade in 1991"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "How many times in United's history have they been relegated?",
      "option_a": "0",
      "option_b": "5",
      "option_c": "3",
      "option_d": "9",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "In the 1998-99 Champions League Final v Bayern Munich, Solskjaer and Sheringham (who came on as substitutes) scored the dramatic goals in the last minute of the game, and then in injury time, to give United a 2-1 win. Which two players were replaced by Solskjaer and Sheringam?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes & Roy Keane",
      "option_b": "Nicky Butt & Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Jesper Blomqvist & Andy Cole",
      "option_d": "David Beckham & Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Jesper Blomqvist & Andy Cole"
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "When Andy Cole signed from Newcastle United, who went the other way as part of the deal?",
      "option_a": "Robbie Savage",
      "option_b": "Dion Dublin",
      "option_c": "Paul McGrath",
      "option_d": "Keith Gillespie",
      "correct": "Keith Gillespie"
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "Who scored the winning goal in the 1990 F.A. Cup final?",
      "option_a": "Brian McClair",
      "option_b": "Lee Martin",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Gary Pallister",
      "correct": "Lee Martin"
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "Shinji Kagawa scored his first and only Manchester United hat-trick against which club?",
      "option_a": "Norwich City",
      "option_b": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_c": "Everton",
      "option_d": "Portsmouth",
      "correct": "Norwich City"
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "question": "Diego Forlan scored his first United goal against which club?",
      "option_a": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_b": "Maccabi Haifa",
      "option_c": "Aston Villa",
      "option_d": "Panathinaikos",
      "correct": "Maccabi Haifa"
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "question": "Teddy Sheringham made 149 appearances in a United shirt. How many goals did he score?",
      "option_a": "56",
      "option_b": "86",
      "option_c": "46",
      "option_d": "66",
      "correct": "46"
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "question": "Which of these United players retired with 129 caps for their country?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_c": "Edwin Van Der Sar",
      "option_d": "Wayne Rooney",
      "correct": "Peter Schmeichel"
    },
    {
      "number": 23,
      "question": "In the 1985 FA Cup Semi-Final replay Manchester United defeated Liverpool 2-1. Which two players scored United's goals?",
      "option_a": "Gordon Strachen & Paul McGrath",
      "option_b": "Frank Stapleton & Norman Whiteside",
      "option_c": "Mark Hughes & Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Graeme Hogg & Norman Whiteside",
      "correct": "Mark Hughes & Bryan Robson"
    },
    {
      "number": 24,
      "question": "Which of these players has the most appearances for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_b": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_c": "Gary Neville",
      "option_d": "Bill Foulkes",
      "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
    },
    {
      "number": 25,
      "question": "Wayne Rooney scored how many goals in europe for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "34",
      "option_b": "36",
      "option_c": "39",
      "option_d": "45",
      "correct": "39"
    },
    {
      "number": 26,
      "question": "How many Manchester United players have won the Ballon d'Or whilst wearing the United shirt?",
      "option_a": "2",
      "option_b": "4",
      "option_c": "6",
      "option_d": "8",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "number": 27,
      "question": "Wayne Rooney scored 10 of his 34 goals in the Champions League against two Italian teams. Who were they?",
      "option_a": "Roma & AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Inter Milan & Juventus",
      "option_c": "Roma & Inter Milan",
      "option_d": "AC Milan & Inter Milan",
      "correct": "Roma & AC Milan"
    },
    {
      "number": 28,
      "question": "How many goals did United score on the way to winning the 1999 Champions League?",
      "option_a": "20",
      "option_b": "25",
      "option_c": "29",
      "option_d": "36",
      "correct": "29"
    },
    {
      "number": 29,
      "question": "How many goals did United score on their way to winning the 2008 Champions League final?",
      "option_a": "13",
      "option_b": "20",
      "option_c": "24",
      "option_d": "18",
      "correct": "20"
    },
    {
      "number": 30,
      "question": "Who holds the record for most goals scored in all competitions in one season for United?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_b": "Denis Law",
      "option_c": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_d": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "correct": "Denis Law"
    },
    {
      "number": 31,
      "question": "Cristiano Ronaldo is the most recent player to win the Ballon D'Or in a United shirt. Who was the last person before him?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_b": "George Best",
      "option_c": "David Beckham",
      "option_d": "Denis Law",
      "correct": "George Best"
    },
    {
      "number": 32,
      "question": "George Best shares the record for most goals scored in one game for United with 6. Who does he share it with?",
      "option_a": "Harold Halse",
      "option_b": "Dimitar Berbatov",
      "option_c": "Andy Cole",
      "option_d": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "correct": "Harold Halse"
    },
    {
      "number": 33,
      "question": "How many Champions League goals did David Beckham score for United?",
      "option_a": "15",
      "option_b": "10",
      "option_c": "20",
      "option_d": "5",
      "correct": "15"
    },
    {
      "number": 34,
      "question": "Manchester United beat Real Madrid on the way to winning the 1968 European Cup. What was the score in the away leg?",
      "option_a": "2-1",
      "option_b": "3-3",
      "option_c": "1-0",
      "option_d": "4-1",
      "correct": "3-3"
    },
    {
      "number": 35,
      "question": "Dwight Yorke led United's goalscoring charge in the league in the 1998-99 season. How many goals did he score that season?",
      "option_a": "17",
      "option_b": "18",
      "option_c": "19",
      "option_d": "20",
      "correct": "18"
    },
    {
      "number": 36,
      "question": "Who scored the only goal as United beat Palmeiras 1-0 to win the 1999 Intercontinental Cup?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_d": "Roy Keane",
      "correct": "Roy Keane"
    },
    {
      "number": 37,
      "question": "United beat which Ecuadorian team 1-0 to win the FIFA Club World Cup in 2008",
      "option_a": "LDU Quito",
      "option_b": "Aucas",
      "option_c": "Olmedo",
      "option_d": "Guayaquil City",
      "correct": "LDU Quito"
    },
    {
      "number": 38,
      "question": "Against which team did Wayne Rooney score his 100th goal for United?",
      "option_a": "Wigan Athletic",
      "option_b": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_c": "Portsmouth",
      "option_d": "Birmingham City",
      "correct": "Wigan Athletic"
    },
    {
      "number": 39,
      "question": "Against which team did Ole Gunnar Solskjaer score his 100th goal for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Zalaegerzeg",
      "option_b": "Maccabi Haifa",
      "option_c": "West Brom",
      "option_d": "Leeds United",
      "correct": "West Brom"
    },
    {
      "number": 40,
      "question": "Who is the youngest player to make an appearance for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Angel Gomes",
      "option_b": "Duncan Edwards",
      "option_c": "David Gaskell",
      "option_d": "Norman Whiteside",
      "correct": "David Gaskell"
    },
    {
      "number": 41,
      "question": "Who is United's top foreign record goalscorer?",
      "option_a": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_d": "Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy"
    },
    {
      "number": 42,
      "question": "How many goals did Diego Forlan score for United?",
      "option_a": "20",
      "option_b": "17",
      "option_c": "25",
      "option_d": "12",
      "correct": "17"
    },
    {
      "number": 43,
      "question": "Manchester United signed Bryan Robson from which club?",
      "option_a": "West Brom",
      "option_b": "Birmingham City",
      "option_c": "Aston Villa",
      "option_d": "Wolves",
      "correct": "West Brom"
    },
    {
      "number": 44,
      "question": "How many goals did Bryan Robson score for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "95",
      "option_b": "100",
      "option_c": "99",
      "option_d": "82",
      "correct": "99"
    },
    {
      "number": 45,
      "question": "Which goalkeeper holds the record for most clean sheets at United?",
      "option_a": "Alex Stepney",
      "option_b": "Gary Bailey",
      "option_c": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_d": "Edwin Van Der Sar",
      "correct": "Peter Schmeichel"
    },
    {
      "number": 46,
      "question": "Alex Büttner scored on his debut against which club?",
      "option_a": "Bolton Wanderers",
      "option_b": "West Brom",
      "option_c": "Wigan Athletic",
      "option_d": "Chelsea",
      "correct": "Wigan Athletic"
    },
    {
      "number": 47,
      "question": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer scored two goals as United won the Champions league in 1999. One against Bayern Munich and the other against _____?",
      "option_a": "Barcelona",
      "option_b": "Juventus",
      "option_c": "Brondby",
      "option_d": "Inter Milan",
      "correct": "Brondby"
    },
    {
      "number": 48,
      "question": "Marcus Rashford scored two goals on his United debut. Who provided the assist for the 2nd goal?",
      "option_a": "Guillermo Varela",
      "option_b": "Juan Mata",
      "option_c": "Jesse Lingard",
      "option_d": "Joe Riley",
      "correct": "Guillermo Varela"
    },
    {
      "number": 49,
      "question": "Including the qualifying round, who was Manchester United's leading scorer in the 1998/99 Champions League?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Andy Cole",
      "correct": "Dwight Yorke"
    },
    {
      "number": 50,
      "question": "How many goals were scored by Gerard Pique on United's way to winning the 2007/08 Champions League?",
      "option_a": "4",
      "option_b": "0",
      "option_c": "1",
      "option_d": "2",
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "number": 51,
      "question": "From which club did Manchester United sign Javier Hernandez?",
      "option_a": "Necaxa",
      "option_b": "Cruz Azul",
      "option_c": "Chivas",
      "option_d": "Club America",
      "correct": "Chivas"
    },
    {
      "number": 52,
      "question": "From which club did Manchester United sign Lee Sharpe?",
      "option_a": "Torquay United",
      "option_b": "Bradford City",
      "option_c": "Exeter City",
      "option_d": "Southampton",
      "correct": "Torquay United"
    },
    {
      "number": 53,
      "question": "Against what club did Mark Hughes get his first senior hat trick for United?",
      "option_a": "Blackburn Rovers",
      "option_b": "Aston Villa",
      "option_c": "Chelsea",
      "option_d": "Arsenal",
      "correct": "Aston Villa"
    },
    {
      "number": 54,
      "question": "Sir Alex Ferguson's first club signing was Viv Anderson. Which club was be brought from?",
      "option_a": "Leicester City",
      "option_b": "Aston Villa",
      "option_c": "Chelsea",
      "option_d": "Arsenal",
      "correct": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
      "number": 55,
      "question": "Peter Schmeichel scored his only United goal against which Russian club?",
      "option_a": "FC Lokomotiv Moscow",
      "option_b": "Rotor Volgograd",
      "option_c": "Arsenal Tula",
      "option_d": "Ural Sverdlovsk Oblast",
      "correct": "Rotor Volgograd"
    },
    {
      "number": 56,
      "question": "What do Cristiano Ronaldo, Eric Cantona, Andrei Kanchelskis, and Juan Sebastian Veron have in common?",
      "option_a": "All scored on their debut for United",
      "option_b": "All wore the number 7 shire whilst at United",
      "option_c": "First players to play for United from their respective countries",
      "option_d": "All sent off in a Manchester Derby",
      "correct": "First players to play for United from their respective countries"
    },
    {
      "number": 57,
      "question": "Manchester United signed Karel Poborsky from which club?",
      "option_a": "České Budějovice",
      "option_b": "Viktoria Žižkov",
      "option_c": "Sparta Prague",
      "option_d": "Slavia Prague",
      "correct": "Slavia Prague"
    },
    {
      "number": 58,
      "question": "Which Manchester United player was named English Footballer of the Year and PFA Player of the Year in 2000?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Roy Keane",
      "option_d": "David Beckham",
      "correct": "Roy Keane"
    },
    {
      "number": 59,
      "question": "How many Champions League goals did Ruud Van Nistelrooy score for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "36",
      "option_b": "44",
      "option_c": "41",
      "option_d": "39",
      "correct": "36"
    },
    {
      "number": 60,
      "question": "How many Champions League goals did Paul Scholes score for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "15",
      "option_b": "20",
      "option_c": "25",
      "option_d": "30",
      "correct": "25"
    },
    {
      "number": 61,
      "question": "Where did United sign Bryan Robson from?",
      "option_a": "Sunderland",
      "option_b": "West Bromwich Albion",
      "option_c": "Newcastle United",
      "option_d": "Middlesbrough",
      "correct": "west Bromwich Albion"
    },
    {
      "number": 64,
      "question": "Henning Berg was signed for how much when he joined Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "£3.5 million",
      "option_b": "£4.6 million",
      "option_c": "£5 million",
      "option_d": "£7.5 million",
      "correct": "£5 million"
    },
    {
      "number": 65,
      "question": "1983: United won the FA Cup again this year, but who did they play in the final?",
      "option_a": "Brighton & Hove Albion",
      "option_b": "Newcastle United",
      "option_c": "Chelsea",
      "option_d": "Queens Park Rangers",
      "correct": "Brighton & Hove Albion"
    },
    {
      "number": 66,
      "question": "1985: Who scored the winning goal in the FA Cup Final against Everton?",
      "option_a": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_b": "Mark Hughes",
      "option_c": "Norman Whiteside",
      "option_d": "Frank Stapleton",
      "correct": "Norman Whiteside"
    },
    {
      "number": 67,
      "question": "1988: In his first season for United, how many goals did Brian McClair score?",
      "option_a": "30",
      "option_b": "31",
      "option_c": "32",
      "option_d": "33",
      "correct": "31"
    },
    {
      "number": 68,
      "question": "Which player scored more goals for United?",
      "option_a": "Nemanja Vidic",
      "option_b": "Michael Carrick",
      "option_c": "Antonio Valencia",
      "option_d": "Marouane Fellaini",
      "correct": "Antonio Valencia"
    },
    {
      "number": 69,
      "question": "From which Midlands club was Dwight Yorke signed?",
      "option_a": "Birmingham City",
      "option_b": "Aston Villa",
      "option_c": "West Bromwich Albion",
      "option_d": "Coventry City",
      "correct": "Aston Villa"
    },
    {
      "number": 70,
      "question": "Which player won the Player of the Year for the 2020–21 United Womens team?",
      "option_a": "Ona Batlle",
      "option_b": "Katie Zelem",
      "option_c": "Hayley Ladd",
      "option_d": "Mary Earps",
      "correct": "Ona Batlle"
    },
    {
      "number": 71,
      "question": "Who won the Sir Matt Busby Player of the Year award for the 2000/01 season?",
      "option_a": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_b": "Denis Irwin",
      "option_c": "Teddy Sheringham",
      "option_d": "Andy Cole",
      "correct": "Teddy Sheringham"
    },
    {
      "number": 72,
      "question": "Who was the first player to win the Sir Matt Busby Player of the Year award from outside Europe?",
      "option_a": "Antonio Valencia",
      "option_b": "Javier Hernandez",
      "option_c": "Kleberson",
      "option_d": "Gabriel Heinze",
      "correct": "Gabriel Heinze"
    },
    {
      "number": 73,
      "question": "Which team was not in United's Group in the 1999/2000 Group Stage for the UEFA Champions League?",
      "option_a": "Olympiacos",
      "option_b": "Fiorentina",
      "option_c": "Bordeaux",
      "option_d": "Valencia",
      "correct": "Olympiacos"
    },
    {
      "number": 74,
      "question": "Which team knocked United's out of the 1999/2000 UEFA Champions League?",
      "option_a": "Bayern Munich",
      "option_b": " Porto",
      "option_c": "Lazio",
      "option_d": "Real Madrid",
      "correct": "Real Madrid"
    },
    {
      "number": 75,
      "question": "Paul Ince made his Manchester United debut against which club?",
      "option_a": "Millwall",
      "option_b": "Manchester City",
      "option_c": "Crystal Palace",
      "option_d": "West Ham United",
      "correct": "Millwall"
    },
    {
      "number": 76,
      "question": "Eric Cantona was bought from Leeds United in 1992, but which player did Leeds United Chariman Bill Fotherby initially call Martin Edwards to enquire about?",
      "option_a": "Paul Ince",
      "option_b": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_c": "Denis Irwin",
      "option_d": "Gary Pallister",
      "correct": "Denis Irwin"
    },
    {
      "number": 77,
      "question": "How many goals did Eric Cantona score for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "62",
      "option_b": "82",
      "option_c": "102",
      "option_d": "122",
      "correct": "82"
    },
    {
      "number": 78,
      "question": "Who scored the opening goal in Sir Alex Ferguson's final game in charge?",
      "option_a": "Shinji Kagawa",
      "option_b": "Alexander Büttner",
      "option_c": "Javier Hernandez",
      "option_d": "Robin Van Persie",
      "correct": "Shinji Kagawa"
    },
    {
      "number": 79,
      "question": "Manchester United won the 1992/93 Premier League season but failed to win their first 3 games. Who did they win their first game against?",
      "option_a": "Sheffield United",
      "option_b": "Everton",
      "option_c": "Ipswich Town",
      "option_d": "Southampton",
      "correct": "Southampton"
    },
    {
      "number": 80,
      "question": "On the way to winning the 1993/94 Premier League, United lost only two of their first 30 matches, both to the same team and scoreline. Which team was it and what was the scoreline?",
      "option_a": "Liverpool (2-0)",
      "option_b": "Arsenal (2-1)",
      "option_c": "Chelsea (1-0)",
      "option_d": "Aston Villa (3-1)",
      "correct": "Chelsea (1-0)"
    },
    {
      "number": 81,
      "question": "In 127 appearances for Manchester United, Jaap Stam only scored one goal. Against which team did he score?",
      "option_a": "West Ham United",
      "option_b": "Charlton Athletic",
      "option_c": "Leicester City",
      "option_d": "Manchester City",
      "correct": "Leicester City"
    },
    {
      "number": 82,
      "question": "Which player scored more goals for United?",
      "option_a": "Gary Neville",
      "option_b": "David May",
      "option_c": "Phil Neville",
      "option_d": "Ronny Johnsen",
      "correct": "Ronny Johnsen"
    },
    {
      "number": 83,
      "question": "Edwin Van Der Sar played how many times for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "266",
      "option_b": "286",
      "option_c": "306",
      "option_d": "326",
      "correct": "266"
    },
    {
      "number": 84,
      "question": "Odion Ighalo scored how many goals for Manchester United whilst on loan?",
      "option_a": "2",
      "option_b": "3",
      "option_c": "4",
      "option_d": "5",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "number": 85,
      "question": "Henrik Larsson scored how many goals for Manchester United whilst on loan?",
      "option_a": "3",
      "option_b": "4",
      "option_c": "5",
      "option_d": "6",
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "number": 86,
      "question": "Who score the winner Manchester United in their 1992 League Cup Final against Nottingham Forest?",
      "option_a": "Mark Hughes",
      "option_b": "Paul Ince",
      "option_c": "Paul Parker",
      "option_d": "Brian McClair",
      "correct": "Brian McClair"
    },
    {
      "number": 87,
      "question": "Which team did Manchester United NOT play in the knockout stages on the way to the 2008/2009 Champions League Final?",
      "option_a": "Lyon",
      "option_b": "Inter Milan",
      "option_c": "Porto",
      "option_d": "Arsenal",
      "correct": "Lyon"
    },
    {
      "number": 88,
      "question": "Who scored the extra time winner against Crystal Palace in the 2016 FA Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Juan Mata",
      "option_b": "Anthony Martial",
      "option_c": "Michael Carrick",
      "option_d": "Jesse Lingard",
      "correct": "Jesse Lingard"
    },
    {
      "number": 89,
      "question": "Which player scored two goals and won Man of the Match in the 3-0 win against Millwall in the 2004 FA Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_b": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_c": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_d": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "correct": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy"
    },
    {
      "number": 90,
      "question": "As of 2023, how many players have won the World Cup whilst playing for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "5",
      "option_b": "8",
      "option_c": "10",
      "option_d": "12",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "number": 91,
      "question": "Which of these teams did Manchester United NOT play on their way to their 1999 FA Cup Final triumph?",
      "option_a": "Middlesbrough",
      "option_b": "Arsenal",
      "option_c": "Leicester City",
      "option_d": "Liverpool",
      "correct": "Leicester City"
    },
    {
      "number": 92,
      "question": "Who scored the only goal in our 2-1 loss in the 2017 UEFA Super Cup final?",
      "option_a": "Romelu Lukaku",
      "option_b": "Jesse Lingard",
      "option_c": "Paul Pogba",
      "option_d": "Anthony Martial",
      "correct": "Romelu Lukaku"
    },
    {
      "number": 93,
      "question": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy played for 5 seasons at Manchester United. How many times was he our leading top scorer  in all competitions during those seasons?",
      "option_a": "2",
      "option_b": "3",
      "option_c": "4",
      "option_d": "5",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "number": 94,
      "question": "Who was the leading top scorer in all competitions as United won the Premier League in the 1992/93 season?",
      "option_a": "Brian McClair",
      "option_b": "Mark Hughes",
      "option_c": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_d": "Andrei Kanchelskis",
      "correct": "Mark Hughes"
    },
    {
      "number": 95,
      "question": "Who scored more goals for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Clayton Blackmore",
      "option_b": "Jesper Olsen",
      "option_c": "Gordon Strachan",
      "option_d": "Peter Davenport",
      "correct": "Gordon Strachan"
    },
    {
      "number": 96,
      "question": "Manchester United lost to which team who eventually finished runners-up in the 2001/02 UEFA Champions League?",
      "option_a": "AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Bayer Leverkusen",
      "option_c": "Real Madrid",
      "option_d": "Barcelona",
      "correct": "Bayer Leverkusen"
    },
    {
      "number": 97,
      "question": "Which team was NOT in Manchester United's group in the 2000 FIFA Club World Championship?",
      "option_a": "Necaxa",
      "option_b": "South Melbourne",
      "option_c": "Vasco Da Gama",
      "option_d": "Raja Casablanca",
      "correct": "Raja Casablanca"
    },
    {
      "number": 98,
      "question": "Who scored two goals and won man of the match as Manchester United came from 2-0 down to beat Manchester City 3-2 in the 2011 FA Community Shield?",
      "option_a": "Dimitar Berbatov",
      "option_b": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_c": "Nani",
      "option_d": "Anderson",
      "correct": "Nani"
    },
    {
      "number": 99,
      "question": "Manchester United won the Premier League trophy in the 2007/08 season. But who came in second place that season?",
      "option_a": "Arsenal",
      "option_b": "Chelsea",
      "option_c": "Liverpool",
      "option_d": "Everton",
      "correct": "Chelsea"
    },
    {
      "number": 100,
      "question": "Which player succeeded Steve Bruce as captain of Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_b": "Roy Keane",
      "option_c": "Gary Neville",
      "option_d": "Martin Buchan",
      "correct": "Eric Cantona"
    }
  ]
}
